Why didn't you tell me
that happened to you?
What, you think we can't protect you?
I don't want to be a burden.
You probably think…
I'm weak.
I'm doing all of this
because I love you all so much.
It was your brother who gave me orders.
-It was Georgia who did it?
-That's not true!
-Don't push me, Georgia.
-Come on!
I fight back.
Your full payment.
You want to silence me
about what happened?
I thought that's what you wanted.
It's so easy for you
to give up on me, isn't it?
Well…
you never defended me, anyway.
Maybe I really don't know…
how to be a good mother.
If only Patricia knew… I'm trying…
You're getting a little too casual
with me now.
Is that a bad thing?
Just don't get used to it.
We're strictly co-workers.
I'm already gaining her trust.
I'll avenge you.
Boss, he's the one I told you about.
You're Ricardo Salvador's former coworker?
Yes.
What is this about?
How long did you work together?
About a year.
He'd just returned to the Philippines.
What was he like?
He was good.
The truth is, he was really good
at what he did.
He was smart, always had a solution,
and had incredible powers of persuasion.
That's why he was the biggest asset
at our PR firm.
-All right, that's enough.
-That's why he kept getting promoted…
Get to the point. What was wrong with him?
-Wrong with him?
-Yes. What was wrong with him?
Did he have any vices? Any enemies?
Did he do anything wrong?
Or was there anything strange
or suspicious about him?
You know, Ricardo got along with everyone.
We just didn't really hang out
with him when we went out.
Only at events,
but those were part of the job.
When it was time to go home,
he'd head straight home.
Whenever we'd talk about our families,
he never really mentioned anything.
We'd complain about our parents,
our in-laws,
issues with our spouses, our kids.
But Ricardo…
I can't remember anything.
You mean, none of you
ever met his wife or child?
Not once.
He never told us anything personal.
If he had a family,
we never met them.
We just thought
he was a very private person.
I can't remember any coworker
who became really close to Ricardo.
He didn't talk about himself.
It was always just work.
Sir, everything's ready.
Okay, do it.
Whose house is this?
What are we doing here?
Why did you bring me here?
This piano…
That's Mom.
That's Teddy and me when we were kids.
Whose house is this, really?
You have so many questions about your mom.
I just want to help you find the answers.
Why did you bring me here?
To answer your questions.
Your mom lived here.
I spoke to one of your father's
former employees.
He said your mom lived here
until she got sick.
She died here too.
Until the very end,
you and your brother were
the only ones on her mind.
Your mom lived here for a long time.
Except for the caretaker,
she didn't interact with anyone.
Not since she left your family.
Dad didn't want us talking about her.
He always took me to La Familia
so I wouldn't look for Mom.
That's why I never got
to experience being a child.
Do you know why she disappeared?
People used to say she'd left
with another man.
Diana.
According to the records,
that man had already been living
in America for years.
The same year your mom left your family.
She wanted to come back to you,
but Don Lucio did everything he could
to keep her from coming back.
Thank you.
Your mom developed depression
after she gave birth to Teddy.
It might have been postpartum depression.
But she shut herself away in this house
and withdrew from the world.
All this time, I never knew
why Mom did that.
She was so tender and loving.
And…
she was into the arts.
She taught me how to play the piano.
I have so many questions.
Did she get tired of being our mother?
Was I not enough for her?
But I should've gone after her.
Maybe I did something wrong.
I failed her so much as her daughter.
Why are you doing this, Ricardo?
So you can finally get answers
to all the questions you've been carrying.
So you can finally have peace.
Oh.
Come on now. Please don't do this.
I need you to work.
I've still got a lot to do. Come on.
That won't answer back.
Let me.
You seem all worked up from multitasking.
You've no idea.
I need at least ten hands.
Or maybe a twin.
Someone who can help me around here.
Ta-da!
You fixed it? Wow.
It's working now.
Nice. Thanks.
You're going back to school?
That's good, Patricia.
If I pass the entrance exam.
-Does Ms. D know?
-Hey.
What does she have to do with this?
She doesn't need to know.
I got this.
I will pay my tuition fee.
And I think I can study
and work here at the same time.
I'll help you. I am a good tutor.
I'm not a child.
I'm in college.
This is easy-peasy.
Besides…
I don't want you to be my tutor.
You stress me out when you're being…
meticulous.
Oh, wow.
-Meticulous?
-Mm-hmm.
You're really not used
to asking for help, are you?
You already know the answer.
Hmm.
I'll still help you.
You don't have a choice.
Jena, April.
Come here. I've something to ask.
What is it, Dad?
Jena.
Do you know how to sell online?
You mean live selling?
Yes, exactly.
I'd like to sell my products
on the internet.
How do I start?
It's easy, Dad. Here. Give me your phone.
We will create and register your account.
Here.
Dad, are you sure you can do it?
Absolutely.
A lot of our neighbors do it.
They sell all kinds of stuff
and earn a lot.
My soaps and vitamins
are different from the rest.
And come on,
you have a handsome dad.
Do you really think
no one will buy from me?
Wow! I love the confidence!
Impressive.
I'm tired of being belittled.
I want to prove them wrong.
Hey, how's my account?
I got you. It's almost done, Dad.
Hurry up.
-Found you.
-Hmm! Why?
What's that?
Notes from the Burger City
marketing meeting.
Why are you giving it to me?
Ms. D wants you to help her plan
a new campaign for Burger City.
Why me?
I don't know either.
She didn't tell me.
Maybe because
you're new here in La Familia.
Maybe for fresh insights?
Hmm.
None of my ideas are fresh
with all the work I have to do.
I don't know, Patricia.
Maybe it's because
she's reaching out to you.
Or maybe…
it's because she trusts you.
Why don't you just tell her
that you'll go back to school?
What if I don't pass the test?
I'm just adding to her list
of disappointments.
Hmm?
You said you can do it, right?
-Hmm?
-You can do it.
"I love my life."
Oh, great.
Really now? Are we that close?
Stop worrying.
I'll help you with that.
Just call me, okay?
-I can do it.
-Good.
I love my life. I love my life.
I love my life.
Hey, later, okay?
I'll help you study.
Five pesos
for each correct answer you'll get.
Well, be prepared to lose all your coins.
Wrong.
Darn it.
Nineteen, A.
-Correct.
-Yes!
-Hey!
-Time to review.
I need to finish this.
You have to be disciplined with your time.
If you have time for La Familia,
you should also have time to study.
Because that's the only way
we get to accomplish this.
Wrong!
-Wrong?
-Wrong.
Just do it.
The correct answer is…
-A.
-Yay!
Jackpot!
Mm-hmm. Jackpot.
I hit the jackpot with your mistakes.
Hmm.
You got a lot wrong.
-Happy birthday to you
-Give me that.
You're really not used
to asking for help, huh?
Happy birthday
Happy birthday, happy birthday
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday!
They're so sweet with their mom.
A family.
Seems fun.
Let's eat!
-Let's eat!
Yummy.
Eating together. Just being together.
-Family always sticks together.
-Oh!
We could use that.
FAMILY STICKS TOGETHER IN GOOD TIMES
You like it?
Mm-hmm.
Impressive.
And for that,
here's your reward.
Thank you.
Nice. We can use that in TV ads.
It's good.
And that is how
we make Burger City accessible
to every Filipino family.
Same as how they loved Cala Soda.
Good work, good work.
Good work.
Okay.
Good job, Patricia. Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
Carlota.
Is it your lunch break yet?
Let's eat out.
Uh, wait here. My boss just
asked me to do something.
Are these the ones you're selling?
Offer it to your colleagues.
Here's the report
the finance department gave me.
Ask for the fourth-quarter report.
Okay. Will do.
What are you doing here?
We're going out to lunch.
Why do you seem to avoid me?
Haven't you…
moved on?
Don't flatter yourself.
You really don't have
self-awareness, do you?
If I'm hurting,
that's because you took
my daughter away from me.
Do you really think I still care
about you and this woman?
I'm actually grateful
you're no longer in my life.
My life got better without you in it.
Don't worry.
My wife and daughter won't be here long.
I have a business now.
Big time.
Would you like to buy some?
This'll clear your impurities.
Seems like it's not working on you.
I hope it's serious this time.
That's why I can't stand you.
That's just how you are.
All you do is belittle people!
I was just thinking about Patricia.
For once, my daughter can finally rest
from looking after you both.
What did you just say?
Wait a minute! That's enough!
You're so hot headed.
You're furious, aren't you,
because nobody loves you?
I'm sure you're jealous because…
my husband visited me.
Husband? Why?
Are you guys married?
Here's your order.
Why are you mad?
Are you that hungry?
I feel so annoyed.
Do you not like the food?
Why don't you marry me yet?
Where is this coming from?
You've been annulled with Diana
for a long time, right?
But you've never even asked me
to marry you.
Martin, we've already had two kids!
Didn't you say that…
you wanted an extravagant wedding?
I can't give that to you yet.
Yes, you can!
We need to save a bit more
so I can give you what you want.
An extravagant wedding.
With… With a beautiful gown?
And with a 100-person guest list?
And will the reception be in a hotel?
Yes.
But in the meantime,
we need to save up first.
That's all I need to hear.
Assurance.
RICARDO: JONATHAN MARTINEZ
HAS A REPORT ON YOU AGAIN.
What else are the secrets of La Familia?
What happened to Melinda Aragon?
Where is Lucio Aragon's wife
and Diana's mother?
Almost none of us
could find any information,
and there are no pictures
of her online either.
-Even the former employees of La Familia
-It's for her. She might not have eaten.
don't know anything about her.
Is there any truth to the rumor
that Melinda Aragon disappeared
because Don Lucio covered up
a family scandal at that time?
Because his wife ran off with another man?
What other secrets
is the Aragon family hiding?
WHAT HAPPENED TO MELINDA ARAGON?
Let's go.
UNKNOWN: THERE ARE NO SECRETS
THAT CANNOT BE REVEALED.
-What's going on?
-Ricardo… there's…
someone is scaring me.
They messaged--
Enzo, someone is scaring me
through text messages!
-It's there!
-Here? On your phone?
-They're scaring me!
-Ah…
Ah…
-Oh my god!
-Which one here, Ms. D?
It… It should be the last one.
It's not here. I'll have
the IT Department look at this.
Please.
Do you think he's telling the truth?
Even I'm shocked.
Mind you, I know
all the gossip going around.
I never heard of that before.
That means Sir Lucio
is good at keeping secrets.
Come to think of it,
no one knows about this.
But do you think it's the truth?
I don't know.
Psst.
Tell me, can I still recover the message?
Unfortunately, it can't be recovered.
They sent you a disappearing message.
It means once that message
is read and disappears,
it will be automatically deleted.
Diana.
Are you sure someone messaged you?
Of course! I even read it!
I can't go wrong about it!
The only thing we can do
is set up an archiving option
so that this doesn't happen again.
I'll have this reported
to the police, Ms. D.
They might be able to do something.
I'll do it.
Where's Patricia's table?
Ah, here.
You!
-One of you messaged me.
-Diana.
What message are you talking about?
We argued earlier,
and now you're threatening me.
Stop acting innocent!
You are making a fuss without evidence.
It's the truth!
And why would
I message you? Are we friends?
You're both just liars!
Mom. Dad.
Your mom is throwing
accusations at us again.
-Leave us alone, Diana!
-It's the truth.
We don't want to get involved with you.
That's enough.
-Mom.
-Hmm?
Let's go.
Come on.
I don't understand anything she said.
What did she say?
Carlota.
You don't have to do this.
Benjie is here.
Diana.
You were threatened and scared.
I can't leave you.
I'll protect you.
Do you believe me?
Why wouldn't I?
You might think I'm losing my mind, like…
Like what happened to my mom.
That's what they want everyone to think.
You might doubt everyone,
but for me,
I will always choose to believe you.
Your mom is truly going insane.
She's blaming us for things
we've never done!
She was just affected
by that Jonathan's report.
Is that enough reason to blame us?
You also engaged instead of ignoring it.
You're blaming me?
Your father and I were blamed.
Patricia, you're just starting
to get to know your mother.
There are a lot of things
you still don't know about her.
Like what?
I don't know. I don't care anymore.
Dad?
Don't think about it anymore.
Just let her be.
I just want to know
why Mom is being threatened.
We don't know all
the nasty things she's done
for her to be nervous.
Good thing Ricardo was there.
You're putting a meaning to this.
What's wrong with that?
You need to be protected,
and Ricardo is doing that for you.
I can't think about him
like that, Nanny Cora.
Especially now.
I want to know who's doing this to me.
Are you suspecting someone?
Whoever that person is,
has something to do with my past.
They're coming after me.
Thank you very much for the information
about Belinda Aragon.
If that happens,
it'll be the news of the century.
But wait, why are you doing this?
Don't you work for Diana?
Just do your job.
Like we agreed.
Follow all my orders.
We need to talk.
About everything
that's been happening lately.
The threat against you,
the report about Mom.
What? Aren't you wondering
why all this is happening now?
We're already looking
for a solution, Teddy.
Who's "we"?
Ricardo again?
All our problems started
when he came here.
He just got here, he juast showed up.
You think you know him that well already?
Don't you think you trust him too much?
Oh, let's say you're right,
but what's his motive?
Even people I've known
for years are the same.
Even my own flesh and blood
wants to destroy me.
Oh, just admit it, Teddy.
You want to eliminate the person
who's protecting me
from everything.
From people like you.
You only know him
within the four walls of La Familia.
But you don't know him
outside the company.
Come on!
Oh, I would be very interested, Teddy,
if I knew you had no motive
behind everything you're telling me.
See.
I rest my case.
You decide. But let me just tell you this.
That trust is making you soft…
Ms. Diana Aragon.
Ricardo.
Oh, Allan, how are you?
When did you get back to the Philippines?
I came home for good
so I could be with my kids.
I heard you're working at La Familia now?
Word travels fast, huh?
Why did you want to meet with me?
I found out
because someone who also works
at La Familia talked to me.
I thought they were a headhunter.
But they just asked me about you.
I thought maybe you could
get me into La Familia.
Put in a good word for me?
Who talked to you?
Diana Aragon's brother.
Oh, what's wrong with him?
-What's wrong with him?
-Yes, what's wrong with him?
Teddy Aragon.
Do you need help?
No. I got this.
What's that for?
It's just for the activation.
Good luck.
Good luck to you too.
Good luck to us.
I hope our Burger City project
is a success.
I hope so too,
if Ricardo doesn't screw things up.
What do you mean?
I know you guys trust that bastard a lot.
But there's a lot you don't know.
Did you and Sir Ricardo fight again?
If so, can you please leave me out of it?
I already have so much on my mind.
I'm just warning you.
You know what, thanks for the warning.
But let's be honest.
After everything you've done to me,
you're the one
I have a harder time trusting.
Sir, let's go.
All right.
I already warned you, okay?
It's up to you now.
Excuse me.
Oh, are you done?
Can we continue reviewing?
Not yet. Just wait. I still have…
…something to send for Burger City.
You're nervous, huh?
I'm hungry.
I have so much to take care of.
This project at Burger City,
then I'm also helping out
with my father's business.
I still have a lot of orders
for toasted siopao,
and then we have to review.
So, can you still review?
Hey.
You can't give up, okay?
I've never given up, not even once.
My family's counting on this. I know that.
That's why sometimes I wonder…
…what if I put my studies on hold again?
Wouldn't it be better if I let
my siblings finish school first?
That way, I can help more
with my father's business
and do my job at La Familia properly.
Oh, my notebook!
Where's my notebook? Is it there?
Where did I put it?
It was just here.
Hmm.
You're pretty careless, huh?
But you're a good person, Patricia.
Your family is lucky to have you.
But I feel like
you need to admit to yourself
that you're struggling.
So reviewing this
is the least of your priorities.
I'm not. I can still handle it.
That's why you put off reviewing,
because you feel like it's for you.
You feel guilty…
for doing something for yourself.
You have to save some time
for yourself, Patricia.
Because if you always put
other people first,
you'll eventually run out of yourself.
And when you're all drained,
what will you have left to give someone?
Okay, I'll review now.
Don't cry anymore.
-It's because of you.
-Oh, why me?
You called me careless.
It's not like you can't take a joke.
You know you're just hungry.
You forget to eat. Eat first.
Let's eat first, then we'll review.
-Right?
-Yes, that's right.
Teddy.
Philip, from Business School. Remember?
We were classmates.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
Congratulations, by the way,
on your venture with Burger City.
Our biggest competitor!
-Yes!
-I'm from Big Bites.
Oh.
The collaboration between
La Familia and Burger City
looks great, doesn't it?
I'm sure you're going
to give us a hard time
as business competitors.
To be honest,
I think the news is already
all over the business world.
What happened to you
and your reassignment.
I feel sorry for you.
Well…
I don't need your pity.
Excuse me.
What if I told you I can
give you what you need?
What do you mean?
You shouldn't make La Familia
a dead end for you, Teddy.
There are a lot of options out there.
Just like our company.
As a former classmate and a friend,
I can help you.
Waiter. Two, please.
All right. I'm listening.
I love my life.
Are you nervous, Patricia?
Enzo!
What are you wearing?
You're so red.
Red is a lucky color to wear for an exam.
-Don't you know that?
-Ah…
Sure.
Wait a minute. What are you doing here?
I'm here to make sure you take the exam.
Oh, I have a good luck charm for you.
Here.
A pencil I sharpened myself.
Use this for your exam.
Because they say someone taking an exam
should use a pencil that was sharpened by…
an intelligent person.
Oh, boy!
-Unbelievable!
-Mm-hmm.
Right?
Good morning.
Please proceed inside for the exam.
Hey.
Don't be nervous.
You prepared for this. Okay? You got this.
Go ahead.
"Good luck on your exam. You've got this."
Where's Diana?
-Mr. Borja, Diana isn't here.
-She has a meeting off-site.
How could you let this happen, Ricardo?
They copied our project almost exactly.
There might have been a leak.
Leak? You better get
to the bottom of this.
A leak?
What happened?
Here, take a look.
The entire campaign is canceled.
But we shouldn't stop looking
for whoever leaked the campaign.
I'll take care of it.
Whoever did this is going to pay.
I'll destroy them. All of them!
Mark my words.
Whoever did it,
they're going to regret the day
they decided to cross me.
Hey, Genevieve!
There's one more concept
that needs a deck.
Isn't it done yet?
Double-check all the data, okay?
We have no room for errors.
-Yes, sir.
-Everyone, listen up!
We have to make this work, okay?
I want everyone to give it their all.
Okay?
-Let's get to work!
-Yes, sir.
This concept highlights transparency
and community engagement.
So, what do you think?
I don't know about you, but I, uh…
I found it all a bit underwhelming.
If it doesn't work for you,
we have other options.
-Mm-hmm?
-Diana made sure of it.
Oops! You can't doze off!
Coffee, guys! Sir Enzo's treat!
Thank you, Lala.
Hannah, here are
the historical files we need.
See if we can use anything from these.
Hey, any news?
Your exam results
are coming out today, right?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Relax.
Breathe, okay?
You got this.
You're going to pass. I'm sure of it.
Keep me posted, okay?
Is that it?
Take a look.
Enzo…
What's wrong?
Let's open it together.
-Okay?
-Okay.
-Ready?
"We are pleased to inform you
that you qualify to be admitted
for the continuing education program."
-You passed!
-I passed!
You passed!
I knew it! I knew it!
You passed, Patricia!
You did it! You did it!
Congratulations, Patricia.
I knew you could do it
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Enzo.
So something good
can still happen in my life.
-I told you.
-Thanks for believing in me.
It was all worth it!
-How do we do it again?
-Like this?
-Like this, not like that!
-Oh, it isn't!
Good job!
Dad? Mom?
I'm home!
April! Jena!
April!
Dad! Mom!
-Go on, eat up.
-Are you having fun?
-Do you like the food?
-It's delicious.
Eat up, okay?
Mm. Wait a sec.
It's Patricia.
-Hello?
-Dad?
Dad, where are you?
I'm eating out
with your mother and your sisters.
Are you home already?
Your mother said you'd be home late.
I see.
Okay, Dad. I'll see you at home.
Martin, do that later.
The food's getting cold.
You should eat.
We'll bring home some food for you, okay?
Bye.
Okay, Dad. Enjoy.
"Solo celebration."
I still have so much work to do.
What are we doing here?
Is this your solution?
When you're too focused,
you can't see the whole picture.
Just take a step back.
Then you'll see the whole picture.
You'll find a solution.
Come on.
Wow.
Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
-Okay!
Yes. All right. You're good.
MS. D, I PASSED THE EXAM
Enzo?
-Hi.
-What are you doing here?
I heard there was a celebration here.
Oh, wow.
You're something else, huh?
You went here just to celebrate with me?
Why not?
This is a big deal for you.
It's only right that we celebrate it…
…the right way.
What's the "right way" of celebrating?
I know a perfect place for that.
-Come on.
-Hold on!
Hold on.
Give me five minutes.
-Almost there.
-My goodness.
-Careful. To your left.
-Where are we?
-Are we there yet?
-Okay.
We're almost there. And…
Three, two, one…
Surprise!
Oh, wow!
-You like it?
-It looks great!
Look.
I blew all the balloons up myself.
Seriously?!
This is too much!
It's as if I graduated Magna Cum Laude!
Have a seat.
I have another surprise for you.
Here.
Enzo, I can't take this.
That's for you.
That will help you.
You can't use the company's laptop
for your online classes, right?
So, I got you that.
You can use that.
And hello!
Look.
This is where I got the money to buy that.
I emptied the jar.
With all your wrong answers,
I was able to buy a tablet.
-Can you believe that?
-Unbelievable.
You really tend to overreact, huh?
There are more coins in the jar
for my correct answers.
Okay, fine. You win.
I added a little more so I could buy that.
Don't worry about paying me back for that.
Consider that a gift.
Hey. Why are you crying?
This is nice.
Thank you.
You're the only person
who made this occasion special for me.
You know what I learned
when my parents died?
That if you're prepared
for life's challenges,
you should also be prepared
to enjoy life's joys.
Hmm.
Thank you for doing this.
You're welcome.
What's wrong? You seem sad.
No one's ever done this for me before.
Why are you so good to me, Ricardo?
Because I like you, Diana.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
I'm not ready yet.
I understand.
But I'm not Martin.
I won't lie to you.
I won't hurt you.
Did you meet up with Ricardo?
How did you know?
You're smiling.
He's the only person I know
who can make you smile.
Nanny, please.
You know what I've gone through.
I don't know
if I can trust again just yet.
Well, how sure are you
that you're going to get hurt again?
Well, isn't that my life's theme?
Diana, we've been together for years.
I've seen all the times
you built La Familia from the ground.
But when it comes to yourself,
why are you full of doubt?
I can see how Ricardo takes care of you.
He puts you first.
He cares for you.
Diana…
it's time to take care of yourself too.
Give yourself a chance to love again.
I've got Diana wrapped around my finger.
It's only a matter of time…
before she falls in love with me.
And she won't be able to escape.
Please don't tell Ms. D about this.
I don't want any special treatment.
-Patricia! Patricia!
-What happened?
I have to take care of my daughter.
What is this? A family reunion?
You're both going to take care
of your beloved daughter?
Did you come here for me or for Patricia?
I'm just worried about Patricia.
-Why?
-I like her, Ms. D.
I know you're behind all of this!
You set me up!
What would happen to us
if you get kicked out of La Familia?
The more she lets me into her life,
the more I can ruin her.
I will make sure
she loses everything she has.